UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/024 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs
1953-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Local 23-25
6000/024 P
12.11 cubic feet
11.2 linear ft.
Photographs.
This collection includes photographs of the International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU).
5751559
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 14, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Biographical / Historical
UNITE, the Union of Needle Trades, Industrial, and Textile Employees was formed in 1995 after a merger between the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU).
In 2004 they announced they would merge with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) which created UNITE HERE.
Jay Mazur served as president of UNITE from its beginning until his retirement in 2001. Bruce Raynor was elected president at that time and served until the HERE merger.
Scope and Contents
Photographs of members, celebrations, strikes, rallies and various other events are arranged in alphabetical order. Photo negatives and contact sheets are sorted by year.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/024: UNITE Local 23-25 Records 6000/024 AV: UNITE Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/024 PUBS: UNITE Local 23-25 Publications 6000/024 MB: UNITE Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/050: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Files 6000/050 AV: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/050 MB: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/050 P: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/050 PUBS: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Publications
Textile industry, New York (State); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.); UNITE HERE (Organization)
5751559
- Day Care Center - Prior to 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  18 photographs
- Day Care Center - 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  10 photographs
- Day Care Center - 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  13 photographs
- Day Care Center Opening - 1/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  6 photographs
- Day Care Center - 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  8 photographs
- Day Care Center -- 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Officials and Famous People (Box 1, Folder 7)
  68 photographs
- Lu Jing-Hua visit -- 6/1990 (China Trade Unionist in exile) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Visit by Zensen Unionists (Box 1, Folder 9)
  5 photographs
- Dave and Eddie's Good-Bye Party (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Other Day Care Events (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Day Care Center -- 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  2 photographs
- Not so Famous People -- Members, Staff, etc. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  32 photographs
- CLUW (Box 1, Folder 14)
  1 photograph
- APALA (Box 1, Folder 15)
  3 photographs
- GIDC -- 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  45 photographs
- Chinese's Back Pay -- 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  29 photographs
- Back Pay - Manna Sportswear -- D.B. (1978) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Family Blue Cross Benefits - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Benefits Registration -- 5/1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  7 photographs
- Gant Boycott (Box 1, Folder 21)
  15 photographs
- GUESS Boycott (Halloween) (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 1994 contract Talks; Leafleting (Box 1, Folder 23)
  9 photographs
- 1988 Negotiations (Box 1, Folder 24)
  4 photographs
- 1991 Negotiations (Box 2, Folder 1)
  75 photographs
- Contract 1994 (Ind. Shop, Rep. Seminar, 1/1994) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 1989 ILG Convention (Box 2, Folder 3)
  1 photographs
- Convention - Mery Cee (Box 2, Folder 4)
  19 photographs
- AFL-CIO Convention (Box 2, Folder 5)
- UNITE Convention - July 1999 -- 1st UNITE Convention (Box 2, Folder 6)
  24 photographs
- Back Pay Demos, etc. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- CPR Classes (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Pre-Natal Care Class -- 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Pre-Natal Class -- 1991- (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Pre-Natal Classes (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Textbook Scholarship -- Awards Ceremony (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Union Health Center (Box 2, Folder 13)
- A Graduation or Certificate presentation -- UNITE First Aid Team (Box 2, Folder 14)
  40 photographs
- Unity House Health Fair Weekend -- 1989; Health Fair -- 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Spring Conference (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Korean Workers at Health Center -- 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  54 photographs
- Chinese Health Center -- 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  46 photographs
- Health and Safety (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Housing -- 1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 1988 -- Christmas (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Health Conference (s) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  60 photographs
- Chinese New Year 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  16 photographs
- 1989 -- X-Mas Celebration (Box 3, Folder 3)
  17 photographs
- Chinese New Year - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- X-Mas -- 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Chinese New Year -- 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Korean Workers at Health Care Center (Box 3, Folder 7)
  39 photographs
- Re-Opening of the Union Health Center (Box 3, Folder 8)
  11 photographs
- Chinese New Year (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Chinese New Year 1974 -- Blay: the moon story (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Chinese New Years -- 1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Chinese -- 1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Chinese New Year -- 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Chinese New Year (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Chinese New Year -- 1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- X-Mas -- 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  12 photographs
- X-Mas -- 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Chinese New Year -- 1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Christmas -- 1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Chinese New Year -- 1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Labor Day: 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  25 photographs
- Labor Day -- 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  14 photographs
- Solidarity Day II (Labor Day 1991) (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Workers' Memorial Day 1992 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Asian Labor Festival -- 1992, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Labor Day -- 1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  37 photographs
- Labor Day -- 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Labor Day Parade -- 1989, 1990 & 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Asian Labor Fest -- 1989 & 1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO (Box 4, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO -- Lane Kirkland (Box 4, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO -- Tom Kahn (Box 4, Folder 3)
- ART (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Asian Labor Committee (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Associate ILGWU Member (AIM) (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Ben Ice Memorial Mass -- 1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  22 photographs
- Health Care, Shop meeting, Worker's Memorial Day (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Buildings (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Catholic - Labor Mass (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Celebrations - Asian Labor Festival (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Celebration - Asian Labor Festival -- 1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Celebrations -- Asian Labor Festival -- 1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Celebrations - Heroines of Labor (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Celebrations -- Holiday Party (Box 4, Folder 15)
  51 photographs
- Celebrations -- Immigration (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Celebrations -- Labor Day (Box 4, Folder 17)
  27 photographs
- Celebrations - Labor Day -- 1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Celebrations -- Union Dance (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Celebrations -- Liberty and Union (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Celebrations -- Local 23 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Celebrations -- Local 23-25 Parade (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Celebrations -- Local 102 March (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Celebrations -- May Honored (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Celebrations -- Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 25)
  56 photographs
- Celebrations -- Miscellaneous Parades (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Celebrations -- New Year's Day (Box 4, Folder 27)
  30 photographs
- Celebrations -- Opening of Chinatown Office -- 1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Celebrations -- OPUS -- 70-70 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Celebrations -- Performances (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Celebrations -- Worker's Memorial Day (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Celebrations -- Yule Shi Hum (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Children (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Chin, Wing Fony (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Chinese Members (Box 5, Folder 1)
  21 photographs
- Civil Rights - Anti-Apartheid Demonstration (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Civil Rights -- Coalition Against Anti-Asian Violence (CAAV) -- First Public Event -- 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Civil Rights - Kmart Strike (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Civil Rights -- Labor Law Reform (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Civil Rights -- Marches and Rallies (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Civil Rights -- Peerless Campaign (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Civil Rights -- Proposition 187 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Coalition of Union Women (CLUW) (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Collective Bargaining (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Compensations and Benefits (Box 5, Folder 11)
  33 photographs
- Compensations and Benefits (2) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  23 photographs
- Conventions - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA) Convention -- 1997, San Francisco (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Conventions -- ILGWU Convention 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Conventions -- ILGWU 40th Convention 1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Culture week, November 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Day Care - Celebrations, Parades (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Day Care Center (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Day Care - Children (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Day Care -- Children's Day on the hill - 1989 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Day Care -- Chung Pak Building (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Day Care -- Chung Pak Child Care Fund (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Day Care - Fundraising Dinner (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Day Care - Fundraiser Fashion Show (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Day Care - Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown Opening (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Day Care - Graduation (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Day Care - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Conventions - ILGWU Convention 1992 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  38 photographs
- Conventions - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Conventions - Moving Forward Together (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Day Care - Play Ground (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Day Care -- Thanksgiving (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Day Care -- Three Kings Day (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Education - Award Ceremonies (Box 6, Folder 4)
  34 photographs
- Education - Chinese class and graduation (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Education -- Chinese English Class Graduation (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Education - Chinese English and Citizenship Classes and Graduation -- 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Education - Classrooms (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Education -- English Classes (Box 6, Folder 9)
  20 photographs
- Education -- English as a second language (ESL) Graduation (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Education -- Exercise and Health Workshop (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Education -- Flower Arranging Class (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Education -- Jay Mazur (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Education -- Leafleting - No Sunday Work (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Education - Marches (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Education -- Meetings, Seminars (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Education -- Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 17)
  52 photographs
- Education -- New Members Class 1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Education -- Pines Seminar (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Education -- Scholarships 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Education - Scholarship and Essay Contest Winners 1986 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Education - Shops Rep Seminar -- November 1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Education -- Shop Rep. Seminar - February 1992 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Education - Shop Rep. Training/Meeting (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Education -- Textbook Scholarship Award (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Education -- Wins Sportswear Health and Safety Training (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Education -- Worker Family Program 1989 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Education - Worker Family Program - 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Education - Worker Family Program -- 1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Education -- Worker Family Program - 1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Education - Worker Family Program -- 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Education - Worker Family Program - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Election Campaigns - Clinton-Gore (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Election Campaigns - Cuomo (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Election Campaign - Dinkins 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Election Campaign - Dinkins -- 1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Election Campaign - Dinkins -- 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Election Campaigns - Michael Dukakis (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Election Campaigns - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Election Campaigns - Mondale/Ferraro (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Executive Board Meetings - 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Executive Board Meetings -- 1990 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Executive Board Meetings -- 1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT) Technology Demonstration (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC) (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Garment Workers' Justice Center (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Health Care - Examinations (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Health Care - Lobbying -- March 17, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Health Care -- Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Health Care - National Emergency Drive for Health Care - October 8, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Health Care - National health Care Rally - June 3, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Health Care - Rallies (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Health Care - Union Health Center (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Health Care - United for AIDS Action - March and Rally -- July 14, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Health Care - Upper South Dept. (Box 7, Folder 28)
- ILGWU Community Work (Box 7, Folder 29)
- ILGWU Style Shows (Box 7, Folder 30)
- International Relations (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Imports - Parades (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Imports - Rallies (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Imports - This Rack is empty (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Jackson, Jesse (Box 7, Folder 35)
- The Killing Floor (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Leafletting (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Legislative (Box 7, Folder 38)
- International Textile, Garment, and Leather Workers' Federation (ILGWF) - Meeting in Capetown, November, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Local 23-25 Election - 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Local 62-32 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Local 132-98-102 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Mazur, Jay (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Meetings - Jay Mazur (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Meetings - MAP Spring Conference - 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Meetings - Miscellaneous (1) (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Meetings - Miscellaneous (2) (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Meetings - Shop meeting (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Meetings - Shop Rep meeting - May 27, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Meetings - Spring Conference (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Members Portraits (Box 8, Folder 12)
  61 photographs
- Membership meetings 1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 14)
  48 photographs
- NAFTA (Box 8, Folder 15)
- NAFTA - Anti-NAFTA Demonstration 1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- NAFTA - Anti-NAFTA Demonstration 1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Solidarity - Convention 1999 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Negotiations (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Solidarity - CUNY (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Negotiations - 1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Negotiations - NY Start Opening Negotiations - March 22, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- OSHA Reform (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Organizational Campaign (Box 8, Folder 22)
- People (1) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  41 photographs
- People (2) (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Personalities - A-L (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Personalities -- M-Z (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Personalities - Unidentified Asian Females (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Personalities - Unidentified Asian Male (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Personalities - Unidentified Males (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia, South Jersey District Council, ILGWU (Box 9, Folder 7)
  36 photographs
- Rallies - 1199 Contract Rally 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Rallies - Against Police Brutality (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Rallies - DC Statehood (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Rallies - Disney Rally (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Rallies - Garment Workers Rally (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Rallies - Housing Now (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Rallies - ILGWU Chinatown, June 24, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Rallies - Local 74 SIEU Rally - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Rallies - March for Women's Lives Rally - 1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Rallies - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Rallies - No Jails - 1982 - Chinatown (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Rallies - Sweatshop Rally in Garment District (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Rallies - Textile Bill Rally 1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Rallies - UNITE! (Box 9, Folder 21)
  26 photographs
- Rallies - UNITE! Rally, August 28, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  44 photographs
- Rallies - Washington DC (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Retirees - 1992 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Retirees - Art Class (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Retirees Club Meeting - 1989 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Retirees - marches and Rallies (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Retirees - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Retirees - Pre-retirement Seminar - 1991 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Retirees - Retirement Planning Seminar (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Romney, Edgar (Box 10, Folder 1)
  43 photographs
- SAE GAE Massacre (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Shop Photos -- 1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Shop Photos - before 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Shop Photos - Color, Enlargements (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Shop Photos - Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC) Class (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Shop Photos - Garment Workers (1) (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Shop Photos - Garment Workers (2) (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Shop Photos - Jay Mazur (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Shop Photos - Members (1) (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Shop Photos - Members (3) (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Shop Photos - Modern Sweatshop (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Shop Photos - Scenes (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Shop Photos - Shop Poster (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Shop Photos - "The Global Assembly Line" (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Shop Photos - Tours (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Solidarity - Convention 1999 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Solidarity - CUNY (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Solidarity Day 1991 - Easton, PA (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Solidarity - Eastern Strike (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Solidarity - Greyhound Strike (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Solidarity - International Association of Machinists (IAM) (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Solidarity - LCAA Demo Against Buthelezi (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Solidarity - March (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Solidarity - NYNEX Strike 1989 -- Communication Workers of America (CWA) (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Solidarity - Pittston Strike, United Mine Workers of America (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Solidarity - Poison grapes, United Farm Workers (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Solidarity - Professional Air Traffic Controllers Organization (PATCO) (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Solidarity - Steelworkers Strike (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Solidarity - UWVA Local 1-2 Rally (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Sports and Recreation (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Strikes 1982 Chinatown Rally/Strike (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Strikes - 1982 Chinatown Rally/Strike (Set-up and March) (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Strikes - 1982 Chinatown Rally/Strike (Speakers) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  28 photographs
- Strikes - Adidas (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Strikes - Chinese (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Strikes - Coy Eklund (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Strikes - Daily News Strike - 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Strikes - Dublin Town Inc. (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Strikes - Dynasty Mfg. Co. 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Strikes - El Paso Strike - 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Strikes - Fashion Headquarters Corp. (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Strikes - GAP (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Strikes - GOYA Protest 1999 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Strikes - Greyhound - Eastern - Domsey Strike (1) (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Strikes - Greyhound - Eastern - Domsey Strike (2) (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Strikes - Guess (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Strikes - Hotel Casino (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Strikes - International Longshore and Warehouse Union (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Strikes - Jerrax Imports (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Strike - Joseph Vincent Strike (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Strikes - Ju-El Mfg. Co. (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Strikes - Judy Bond Strike (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Strikes - Lasting Impressions Inc. (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Strikes - Leslie Fay Strike - June 9, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Strikes - L.I.F. Factors Corp. (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Strikes - Lord & Taylor (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Strikes - Miner's Strike 1993 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Strikes - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Strikes - Other Organizations (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Strikes - Parima Strike (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Strikes - Rain Fair Strike 1991 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Sweatshops (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Sweatshops - Washington, DC - Lobby Day -- July 27, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Tiananmen Square Massacre Protest - NYC -- June 9, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Triangle Fire Commemoration (Box 11, Folder 33)
  59 photographs
- Union Label (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Union Label (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Union Label - Hillary Clinton (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Voting - Marches (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Voting - Voter Registration (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Worker's Memorial Day 1989 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Chinatown Liberty Fair and Veto the Veto March - Washington (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Contacts and negatives: John Cole, Photographer (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Contacts and negatives: Pat Gouduis, Photographer (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Contacts and negatives - 1980: Earl Dotter, Photographer (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Contacts - 1982: Images Unlimited (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Eastern Picket, March 18 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Negatives (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Negatives (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Negatives log sheets (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Photo negatives and Contact Sheets -- 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Photo negatives and contact Sheets -- 1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Photo negatives and contact Sheets -- 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Contacts and negatives -- 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1987 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Contacts and Large negatives, slides -- 1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  10 slides
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Contacts and negatives -- 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Photo Contact sheets and Negatives -- 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets -- 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous photos, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  9 photographs -- one is labeled - 29th convention, International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, Atlantic City, N.J. -- May 10-18, 1956
- Rallies (Box 17, Folder 2)
- UNITE -- Conventions (Box 17, Folder 3)
- UNITE (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Rally (Box 17, Folder 5)
- 1999 UNITE Convention (Box 17, Folder 6)
- John Marazita (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Irving Margulies (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Local 23-25 UNITE! (Box 17, Folder 9)
- UNITE (Box 17, Folder 10)
  appears to be an awards ceremony -- 35 photographs
- Conference (Box 17, Folder 11)
- May Chen (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Awards ceremony (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Parties (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Staff Benefits (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Contact Sheets (Box 17, Folder 17)
- May Chen (portrait shots) (Box 17, Folder 18)
  53 photographs
- Photo negatives and Contact sheets (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Labor Day 1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- X-Mas 2003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  76 photographs